<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Audio Effects Express©</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Getting Started -->
    <string name="start_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="start_text">Choose an effect to get started or the tutorial button in the upper right-hand corner to learn how to operate the application and get more technical information.</string>

    <!-- Reverb -->
    <string name="reverb_effect_name">Reverb</string>
    <string name="reverb_effect_desc">Add an echo</string>
    <string name="reverb_tutorial">
        Reverb or Echo functions are used to simulate the effect of
        reverberation in a large hall or cavern. Several delayed signals
        are added to the original recorded signal to add the echo effect.
        For this application\'s purposes, the original sounds data is repeated
        in short bursts and added to the original signal. These repeats have
        diminishing effects so the echo effects don\'t last forever and do
        eventually die off.</string>

    <!-- Lowpass -->
    <string name="lowpass_effect_name">Lowpass Filter</string>
    <string name="lowpass_effect_desc">Remove high pitch noise</string>
    <string name="lowpass_tutorial">
        The low pass filter on this application only passes data
    from the signal under a certain range. The range is
    determined by the signal so this is not a set value.
    When you play back the signal, only lower amplitude sounds
    will be played back because the filter will capture the
    higher amplitude data points.</string>

    <!-- Highpass -->
    <string name="highpass_effect_name">Highpass Filter</string>
    <string name="highpass_effect_desc">Remove low pitch noise</string>
    <string name="highpass_tutorial">The high pass filter on this application only passes data
        from the signal over a certain range. The range is
        determined by the signal so this is not a set value.
        When you play back the signal, only higher amplitude sounds
        will be played back because the filter will capture the
        lower amplitude data points. </string>

    <!-- Reverse -->
    <string name="reverse_effect_name">Reverse</string>
    <string name="reverse_effect_desc">Reverse the recording</string>
    <string name="reverse_tutorial">The reverse function in this application takes the last sample
        and makes it to the first and takes the first sample and
        makes it the last. It does this for all the data points in the
        middle as well. So the sound you hear will sound backwards to
        what it originally was. The audio waveform should also look
        backwards from what it originally looked like when you recorded
        your signal.</string>

    <!-- Halve Samples -->
    <string name="halve_effect_name">Halve Samples</string>
    <string name="halve_effect_desc">loss in quality</string>
    <string name="halve_tutorial">Also referred to as Decimation, this is the process of
        reducing the sampling rate of a signal. Decimation reduces
        the data rate of the size of the data, in this application\'s
        case we reduce the size by half. This can also cause
        degradation of the signal because you are cutting out
        important pieces of data from the signal.
    </string>


    <string name="halve_sample_text">Halve Sample</string>

    <string name="halve_sample_title">Halve Sample</string>

    <string name="double_sample_text">Double Sample</string>

    <string name="double_sample_title">Double Sample</string>

    <!-- Double Samples -->
    <string name="double_effect_name">Double Samples</string>
    <string name="double_effect_desc">stretches recording</string>
    <string name="double_tutorial">Also referred to as <i>Interpolation</i>, this is the process of
        creating new data points within the range of the known
        data points. This can be done by converting a sampled
        digital signal (such as a recording of your voice) to a
        higher sampling rate. In this application\'s case,
        the sample rate is multiplied by two.</string>

    <!-- App Info -->
    <string name="appinfo_effect_name">Application Basics</string>
    <string name="appinfo_tutorial">1. Press Rec and start speaking in a normal voice.\n2. Press stop when
        finished.\n3. Select function button you want to apply.\n4. Press Play button to listen to your signal.</string>

    <!-- K-State Engg Info -->
    <string name="engg_effect_name">K-State Engineering</string>
    <string name="engg_tutorial"><b>Vision Statement:</b>\nThe Kansas State University College of Engineering will
be a highly ranked college providing quality education
within a research environment that develops engineering
leaders to benefit society.\n\nPlease visit http://www.engg.ksu.edu\nLike us on
        Facebook: K-State Engineering\n\nUndergraduate enrollment: 3,503\nUndergraduate degrees
        granted: 531\nTenured, tenure-track faculty: 123\nEndowment: $147M</string>

    <string name="title_activity_display_tutorial">DisplayTutorial</string>

</resources>
